<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Baber Custom Builders</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Baber Custom Builders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Commercial Buildout</title>
      <link>/services/commercial-buildout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/commercial-buildout/</guid>
      <description>Baber Custom Builders has years of experience with creating custom office space from a blank canvas. Our work includes several medical facilities, and a large church.
Medical facility experience We have built out space for several chiropractors and vision clinics, and have the experience to understand the unique needs of these businesses such as: custom X-ray rooms, reception counters, and quiet rooms for sensory experiences and personal medical conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decks &amp; Fencing</title>
      <link>/services/decks-fencing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/decks-fencing/</guid>
      <description>We have built decks from scratch, resurfaced existing structures with new flooring, and corrected structural issues.
Deck Building Many decks are not built to withstand years of use, and exposure to the elements. We can help build a new deck or improve the one you have. Experience working with exotic woods, composite materials, and standard treated lumber.
Fencing Experience with privacy fencing and landscape partitions for privacy and architectural interest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remodels</title>
      <link>/services/remodels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/remodels/</guid>
      <description>Interior remodeling is one of our primary specialities, and our experience ranges from simple one-room changes all the way up to complete house remodels and everything in between.
Basic Remodels Tired of that popcorn ceiling ?
Maybe you need a new door, a couple new windows, or want to open up a wall between your kitchen and living space.
We&amp;rsquo;ve done all of this and more. Contact us now to setup an appointment to review your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Residential Bathrooms</title>
      <link>/services/residential-bathroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/residential-bathroom/</guid>
      <description>Baber Custom Builders has specialized in bathroom remodels for years, and built a reputation on functional well design spaces with timeless appeal.
Tile Showers We have built stand-up showers and tiled tower/tub combos for many satisfied customers.
Custom Cabinetry We often work with cabinet makers to build custom cabinetry for your project, but can also install stock cabinetry to stay within your project budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Residential Kitchens</title>
      <link>/services/residential-kitchen-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/residential-kitchen-remodel/</guid>
      <description>Let us help you modernize your kitchen with new flooring, cabinets, and fixtures. We can help you realize your dream kitchen.
Small Remodel We can help with small remodeling work in your kitchen such as:
 Backsplash Flooring New fixtures  Full Remodel We also have experience in full kitchen remodels, including cabinetry, plumbing, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trim Carpentry</title>
      <link>/services/trim-carpentry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/trim-carpentry/</guid>
      <description>Baber Custom Builders has completed projects such as built-in entertainment centers, bookshelves, and has done full-house trim work on remodel and new-build construction.
Trim Carpentry Options Previous projects have included work on a wide variety of materials and different spaces. You may need to add matching trim in a newly remodeled area or want to give your house a new look. Whatever the case, we have the experience to help you get the quality trim that you want.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>